Curriculum Vitae

Francisco Vilela Tembo

• 1855 Oak Park Blvd Apt 2, Pleasant Hill CA Cellular (305) 879 2954

Francisco.tembo@atlantisuniversity.edu

Objective

To be hired for a project coordinator position by a progressive organization in order to further my experience that can help me grow professionally while assisting the progressive organization to achieve its business goal of profit increase by providing consistent quality, reliable data integrity and accountant service that always meets and exceeds stakeholders demands.

SKills:

- Self-starter who completes projects prior to assigned deadlines
- Creative researcher who seeks out and finds solutions
- knowledge on standard accounting (GAAP) and regulatory standards
- General business insight on data analysis
- Attention to detail, Effective communication
- Utilize and configure Microsoft Office including Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access and Visio
- Increase company profits by suggestively selling products
- Ability to assist end users with resolving technical issues via phone and in person
- Building, repairing, maintaining and troubleshooting computer systems
- Configuration DNS, Active Directory and Cisco routers and switches
- Inbound call center and online live customer support experience

Education

2013 - 2018:

• Atlantis University in Miami, FL

Bachelor in Management Information Systems

2010 - 2013:

• Business Administration from Diablo Valley College, Pleasant Hill, CA

Experience

2019-2020

• Service technician for Canon Solution of American, Walnut Creek, CA

Onsite technician for our clients and customers, imported and exported needed files Setup network and mapped out infrastructure for our clients,

Meat customer demands by providing efficient, responsive and accurate service support

2017 - 2018

• Call Center Representative at Alorica in Cutler Ridge, Miami, FL

Answered inbounding calls from our Directv/AT&T clients customer

Set up days for the Directv/AT&T technicians to go to the customers new house to set up their cable

Assisted inbounding call customers with their need regarding their cabling

2016 - 2017

- Volunteer as IT Club Member having completed the following projects
 - >Switches and Routers Uploaded
 - > Installing needed software onto the IT Club computers around campus

2014 - 2014

- Hands on technical assignment on IT projects from ITT Technical Institute Hialeah, FL
- Volunteer as IT support team member and IT Club Member having completed the following projects > Imaging 80+ computers throughout the campus.
 Installing all needed software and keeping them up to date.
 - Obtaining experience with switches and routers.
 Assisting in any other manner as needed